I start...ads our own...college study...size a much six from
where he spotted and how we started out I'm very proud these...stories like
...that make me...prong of enormous impact we making the world?
I saw a lot and his innovation
...a very early point I figured this is someone that I can help group.
...in engineer
...at microsoft office every...a get technical suppose from the evangelists
...order platform a bls study does...of sheehan potter
and eventually...aj...imagine cup final in twenty
...nigeria I met...chance the time were bringing windows phone
to nigeria and I figure hey this guy's a smart-guides if we take him now and we
groom him and help them to monetize and
helping to google well we've been two years two years happens to now.
After dabbling in android development started
...on company...as a cu and this company no as a
...of nineteen naps only...windows phone was
all over six million downloads intensive believed...before
...eye-hand games scholarly comb from develop
mission but as the true because it's all depends on...to.
The assumption of a shun absorbing the technology and
...platform can break all the...that are out there and
...this is important because it brings many businesses that
can actually build the economy in...companies...the content...
The fact that a story like this will come out very quickly
form a students to...a business owner...very proud of collectively as
...a company also very...that he's actually been seen as a
...to others as well so
in umbrellas case if we can inspire if we can enabled if we can
support more of his time I think we can begin to make a very limited impact.
Idealize an amazing example of the africa that
we want the road to know about these jan these ambitious
these creative and he's very hardworking of the...is...
All right I have ordered to be with you
...abiola this is an inspiring story so how did you get a
programming.
...as their rights in computer programs on a
Because the that was plugged in computes and,
school was...the none I...uphold
...so ...days...on make them all ...what's...
I love that I mean I was...united states...but the same
passion for from writing codes when something works I think that
...universal...about the first thing you ever...and how what was that feeling
like the default in a...to the kind...dissing game
...it was basically based on things...braid on code
...amazing bins around the world so as a person I just want to
...something like that so I want to lenox program
...window of no-go tendency invests...so, basically...in was awesome of
...for you to see that...this somethin' we brought up the good result...
works...what the and also for...encoding is unique in says
respectable where you are you can...program...the
...the on like...make the mechanical engineer or that's where you need some specific argue
...august...is all about access to...information...to a
...to go that's amazing so you were you were a
finalist in the imagine cup what was it that you wrote and how to go so
back-to-school my server might seeing we saw
the education...was...
...was in...we expected we are going to...to meet of
...so we decided to create some sort of like about...classroom
...when if you have a very good to each other and on a part of the
world is student comes somewhere...does...from that so basically
...what you...create that myself on my team members so, you know, that's a
big barrio of we don't have quality teachers in my school
but if we have no doubt very good suggest somewhere...we can then.
So, this
app would allow people that maybe don't have access to good teachers to have really good
teacher exist somewhere else...that's an inspiring application and of itself
...so now what do you
...thirty give-me company kollo...so games so, yeah, so.
So, it's all-in-all we vibe...that's five games the you so when we added by
...games boa
...to casual games on that...for the windows platform
...future phones...because in avocado got...do you have an
example we can look at of some of your games the average see below video...
So, this...idea and.
Kind of like plates
...upon in society we live in moi.
Society...in what sense and says...for the...them overcomes go out to
...games shows like...afrikaans in
...and...with postulate...is
...it pulleys month taking bribes from the boss conduct online addendum to
...conduct which the trying to run away and becomes it
...I game and lesser and ibm...basically those...you do
and that's not that's all likethat's not easy to do what did you write that in
the so for the pc version...or reaping june
...for windows fluent design unity...so you have
...this is like in the book I the other day I'm not between us
...kind of thing...downloaded unity and I download
unreal and I started getting into it is not trivial stuff this is complicated stuff how did
...so say you want coach being...us I want...a game developers
...set tell me how can eyesore
work-up to learning those technology how-to-do-it
...for...must...the language...is infers
...before I even go to...or...xna
...by games actually...xna most of the games so
...csharp well so basically I go to actually and,
this is a very...moment for me and says bach home every lead to axes
...what's...like see also and,
download some sample...
...to go to it I remember when you had
...china nine and give some examples so basically that...I'll
always able to then because I mean and it's a global world...every information
camby axes any...access to information is all we need
...us...do on my...within got it so what advice
to you have...there's some there's some kid watch now...like she just says hey I want to
be a game developer just like abiola what advice you have to her for her?
I mean as a game develop...you often...does not just about
...lunatics mobileit's a commission of
...on arts so dimitri show descends who...mass
...out-of-court appropriate must...that...algorithm law
than everything demos in easy ashkenazi imagine a
...glossy narrow it makes it very easy for you to top who the
...economic solving that's awesome so how many people
...just your company are you trying to get more people to help you write code so yeah, I
started with me in loon now we of...see mobile that's in
...and yeah,...those we have someone nato's of graphic designso,
it's growing physically that's one of
...best part about this story for me is that you can really be
anywhere and...so definitely and I think the ruins...the
...any parting words for our viewers anything you want to...yeah,
I think ...of...negates work ...helps.
I mean because the biggest part of what you are doin' was what creating information
online...is not...information that open lives because there might be a
...somewhere of the in
...of all the just kind of drain to achieve something and
they will go online see the information on to be of...oebps them I
remembered forced to read I read online and on xna developments
that someone does road story online I'll leave you
basin was expecting to get the reward but then there was a kid day in
...than lenin...step...step on, yeah,
kind of like...me into xna development...so, yeah,...you just sort of
gone up from there I've done so keep...every information...everything, you know,
keep share in...to be open lives of the will thanks so much
...inspire me I feel I feel like I haven't done enough...to match
...you're doing, you know,
what you...me to go out there and writing game...go up there and rights of code or do
...about...technology of your thanks for stopping by into room
...the expect great...their hit respect...great things
...to romans thanks for watching and we'll catch you guys next time take care?